- gasps but I say this thing babies
alive it's totally like your case copies
no but they need the whole thing that's
a great point
all right post the audio on slack yeah
yeah too much the scope is have like
ports to do what up greven do be of
twenty-ninth go beats like clear about
comma dinner nothing credible that's so
kind of you guys hey nice to meet you
guys social media coordinator I compared
my tweet yesterday idle no you told me
they were what did I say
you told me to call me some self-driving
car sober self-driving cars solar
generators are self driving for a solver
Cobra team no that's too much
I was gonna say LinkedIn that X CEO and
no pointer George Hotz gave me that
title yeah cuz there's no CEO right
there in the middle of the table as
please
wait to Korean style for us oh love your
feet going - team oh okay well I really
do shelf in the ship way too much I'm
not that's just not qualified to give
you investment advice got a variety of
things people are consuming so we will
get their food for not just bill now
yeah that's right that's big model
I always big mother it's coming along so
guys we have to do an EOS release before
we can do a great father
this means ship SF
oh the other thing to do that's a good
point
no Roger bear is not an investor in
trauma we need to make something there
is a block yeah yeah these model uses
big power and if charging gate is
already a thing oh yes there will be a
little driving car Awareness Week to our
they're not interested and I will be
putting out the date like for a couple
weeks ourselves but set send me ideas on
slack of where we should go we're going
down south I normally cut George's hair
but he got a haircut I've gotta hurt no
Alex where I asked that but normally
would I think it's the real Alex right
that's about Alex right I'm still
waiting on my my coat that you promised
my friend the Dean was like bro you
gotta read this blogs can't draw across
the country 32 hours they're like a
radar detector go to the East Coast it's
so far from here we probably won't make
it out choices hi everyone that's right
sweat pants but yeah we do love those
sweatpants and gave us brevin I wear
them oh yeah they're really good yeah me
too I really do wear them quite often
okay I'll email you my address that
sounds good pick up 48 we have 64 but
now it's like people are not really
hungry people are hoping you're watching
Harold Lee doesn't report me you gotta
keep Scooby's alive
I will I'll just go we can't fit the
extra block on the wires to virtually
Chris makes a good point that we should
ship him here and we'll make a an epic
vlog series
Oh what cleanup the New York to do you
know what we got today what do we get we
talked about it oh my god who does know
we're talking about I know
we're going ham we don't feed them in la
cama cama merchandise is expanding never
have to go back
we got the comedy back it's a comedy
back and it's actually gonna be to a
surprise
why is life going to have the price of
water oh there we go
this is a bike Friday you don't spin a
lot guys what's the safest day Harold
made a scavenger hunt for the office Oh
super awesome SD cards but Alex Roy is
drive from India for you okay links in
the office but we lost it let's just sit
no we didn't lose anything
karma hoodie gold how do we not think of
that that's a
best year this year oh do is it s here
whatever happened to that hoody that you
use on the van like white with the black
come on oh that was only friend in those
rare the over I can get them now too so
you have to return yours George
Catherine's wooden bride up twice this
dinner mm-hmm summer she's not on iscope
established Oh Alex Alex DUP microscopy
ID by white with black comment instantly
I think we should do gold
we've looked so tax it be amazingly no
there's no way that's I'm gonna be so
red tank top rich that's the tackiest of
the know why do they put us upstairs
it's just like the upstairs section for
large tables but you get forgotten that
they don't even like the candles that's
really sad the design that is the next
opening
I mean drives itself look good it was
like a picture of beer it's all my house
yes this is the second thing that's
happened to us yeah they all surprised
me dessert how many Brazilians are there
no worries without the questions
yeah I can't believe it's still not
there oh it's not a bomb that's totally
wrong
yeah no beer sorry it has to be hot yeah
I agree 45 when are we going to connect
to eons together with whatever things oh
do me on technology we do would be
willing to have two wheels yeah by 2
amps for 2 and 1/2 X the call points oh
yes we're not making it to me again make
your pick actually tell me about you you
used to to us and then you get 2 and 1/2
X the amount of colorpoints or you're
right double de on double the fun double
the profit that is
[Music]
apparently if you want to be a CEO you
have to get you got 2 X 4 km okay I'm
gonna say bye